Our family, our family is progressive,
we have to enjoy it a lot, we have to enjoy it a lot,
stop comedy special, we are a
great actor, we are having fun, we have to enjoy it a lot, special we have to
enjoy it a lot, we are free of cost, we are almost in trouble, we have to take the case in jail, we are in trouble ...  So there was
a wine shop in Nashik, then an
idea came to my mind, let's
start flying, Vidya had four bottles of
wine, the signature was flying, the
driver said, the total was 14 bottles of
alcohol, just imagine,
five bottles of CNG, 14 bottles of liquor, 120
kg of alcohol, ground clearance of Rs. 120 kg, the
car was parked at Gujarat Maharashtra border,
I called and the
driver was driving, the car stopped at the toll naka, at the toll naka, just behind, the
siren was going off, the car started to overtake, it was the
pre-
stage of
driving, the PCR stopped at a very high speed, the constable applied brakes, the car stopped at a kilometer, the
PCR stopped at a distance of 100 km, the
constable stopped the
car, the PCR stopped at a distance of 100 km, the driver
said, driver sir, I asked the
driver to wait for a minute, the driver may talk to me, whatever the driver said, there was immediate
time  The constable came down and
opened the side door and the door of the same seat was
torn. When he heard the sound of the stick, he said to me, "
I will get it done." I
said, "Then take it out. Then I opened the navel button and opened it.
Pushpani was my friend's friend. I was
saving him.
Constable drank water from a distance. Constable drank water,
sir, Simran,
Simran, of my
name, do it.
People are Gujarati, Gujarati,
Gujarati, you were dominant in the negotiations.
If you had reached the
negotiation deal, then the Samwadi
party was dominant. With full confidence,
PI sahib said, what is the problem
today, sir, what is the problem? I have
not bottled it now.
Now I am coming, why should
I ask you a question? In 10 seconds, I am
excellent, I have to say,
18 points, rest
plus, there is this problem sir.  What is
the
problem, he did not inform me, I came out of the
temple for
a second sir, I took 10 seconds to reach there,
I started calling him,
sir once my neighbour's address was
known, I was going to
jail, at one point the
car
reached there, I got a message, I
contacted me, I want
driver information,
you should also keep me on the car, I want to discuss with you,
driver is also
waiting for you, I am on Gujarat Maharashtra border,
police have got some news, I have to
chase you, after some time I
called on 1100,
last dialled, then sir, sir, sir, khaj
sir called, the car was near,
I fell down, the car was hit, mother's
CPR, you saved my life,
amazing friend, no one has made any difference yet, I called
Mentally disturb kare ek vaar
gaad tumne physically disturb kare
[Prasha] B
m ghar
andar rodi
de second par rodi gabay ka
gadi ghar na joti ho to fatafat subscribe kari done
subscribe karelo to video ne
like ane share kari do ane aa reete stand
up enjoy karo manama along with sketch cha i coming very
soon enjoy
[Prasha]
[Music]